

#### **EMPLOYMENT OBJECTIVE**

Experienced auditor seeks to be in an advisory role in a reputable organisation that can develop and utilise the skills and knowledge acquired in my studies and audit career. I am confident of working well in a team and able to deliver results under pressure.

#### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

Financial Analysis	Assurance
Financial Reporting	Project Management

#### **EDUCATION**

CFA PROGRAMSingaporePassed Level I of the CFA Program (Dec 2016)2016 - Current

## INSTITUTE OF SINGAPORE CHARTERED ACCOUNTANTS

Member - Chartered Accountant of Singapore (ISCA PE)

Pending completion of practical experience (July 2018)

## **UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (SIM)**

Bachelor of Science in Accounting and Finance (Second Upper Honours)

First Class Grade in Financial Reporting, Audit and Assurance and Principles of Banking and Finance

TEMASEK POLYTECHNICSingaporeDiploma in Computer Engineering2005 - 2008

## **EXPERIENCE**

## PRICEWATERHOUSECOOPERS LLP

Audit Senior Associate 2, General Assurance Achieved High Performer rating

Full-time

Singapore

Singapore

2010 - 2013

2013 - Current

Nov 2014 - Current

- Performed statutory audit as team-in-charge for public listed and local companies, specialising in real estate industry
- Supervised and guided junior associates in allocated tasks to ensure smooth completion within tight deadlines
- Conducted client interviews and internal meetings to facilitate audit planning and execution
- Performed analysis and examination of financial statements and provided solutions to potential accounting issues
- · Collaborated with global audit offices and specialists on audit engagements
- Identified, communicated and provided solutions on internal controls weaknesses, auditing and accounting matters to clients, managers and engagement partners
- Built and maintained good rapport with the audit team and clients across all levels
- · Managing of budget and resources throughout the engagement

# **DELOITTE & TOUCHE LLP**

Audit Associate Year 2, General Assurance

Full-time

Oct 2013 - Nov 2014

- Perform field work to gather sufficient evidence to express an audit opinion on a company's financial statements
  - Performance of test of controls, analytical procedures and substantive test
- · Provide assistance in drafting the client's financial statements in compliance with IFRS and local corporate laws
- Interact closely with all levels of key personnel within organisations to ensure smooth conclusion of an audit engagement
- Worked on clients across various industries including food and beverage, shipping, travel and tourism, retail and trading

# **ECOVIS ASSURANCE LLP**

Audit Assistant, Assurance

Internship

May 2013 - Aug 2013

- Research and perform test run on new financial audit software (Engagement CS Thomson Reuters)
  - Prepare presentation and guide auditors in using the new software
- Support the planning, execution and delivery of the assurance engagements
  - Ensuring accuracy and completeness of clients' data records for audit purposes
  - Assist auditors in vouching, tracing, proof-reading, casting, sighting and cross-referencing
- Develop and maintain productive working relationships with client personnel